{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "There are ___ children attending school in our village than in your village.",
      "a": "a few",
      "b": "few",
      "c": "less",
      "d": "fewer",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- fewer ... than (the comparative form)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "School being over, there were only a ___ number of students in the playground.",
      "a": "little",
      "b": "small",
      "c": "few",
      "d": "short",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- A small number of + countable nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are they able to start on time? \"No, they are ___ to do so.\"",
      "a": "impossible",
      "b": "incapable",
      "c": "unable",
      "d": "inable",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Be unable to V \n- Be incapable of V-ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The prisoner remained ___ throughout the questioning.",
      "a": "silence",
      "b": "silently",
      "c": "silent",
      "d": "silencing",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Remain + adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I don't think that his watch is ___.",
      "a": "worth the price",
      "b": "worthy the price",
      "c": "worthy to buy",
      "d": "worth of the price",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Be worth + noun = be worthy of + noun = be worthy to V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bookstore did not prepare _________ books for all of the students in the class.",
      "a": "plenty",
      "b": "enough",
      "c": "enough of",
      "d": "as many",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Enough + noun",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do they eat there in Honolulu? \" ___ eat rice rather than potatoes.\"",
      "a": "Most of people",
      "b": "The most of people",
      "c": "Most of the people",
      "d": "The most people",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Most of the + plural nouns \n- Most + plural nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's for dinner? \"I don't know. There isn't ___ food left in the house.\"",
      "a": "none",
      "b": "no",
      "c": "some",
      "d": "any",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Any: used in negative sentences \n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "An invertebrate is an animal with _________ spine.",
      "a": "any",
      "b": "no",
      "c": "not",
      "d": "none",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- No + nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Scientists are searching for the oldest ___ because it can teach them a great deal about many matters.",
      "a": "tree alive",
      "b": "tree lively",
      "c": "tree live",
      "d": "alive tree",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Tree alive: still existing\n- Alive tree: not dead tree",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}